<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Dan Writes</title>
    <link>https://dansramblings.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Dan Writes</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://dansramblings.com/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://dansramblings.com/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dansramblings.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Catch</title>
      <link>https://dansramblings.com/posts/05092024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dansramblings.com/posts/05092024/</guid>
      <description>It was one of those summer days. The beach murmurs played with the staccato seagulls and the hourly melodic jangle of the ice cream truck. The days I would think about in Ms. Pierce&amp;rsquo;s class that would cause me to fidget by fwopping my blue laminate multiplication table back and forth. She&amp;rsquo;d patiently tell me to put it down but I knew that the fwops wore on her because at the end of the year, she retired and moved to Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An imagined scene in &#34;The Grapes of Wrath&#34; sequel</title>
      <link>https://dansramblings.com/posts/story1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dansramblings.com/posts/story1/</guid>
      <description>“Stick aroun’,” said Tom. “Stick aroun’ till tomorra anyways.”
The boy paused. “No. I’m a-goin’”, he said. “I got my min’ made up. I got ta do &amp;rsquo;er.”
“You don’ even know where in the hell you’re goin’.”
“Yeah but I jes’ know”.
Tom sighed. He had felt the same way. In fact when he was seventeen an article in the Oklahoman caused him to hitch rides for twenty days to Topeka just to see that new capitol building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cast</title>
      <link>https://dansramblings.com/posts/story2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dansramblings.com/posts/story2/</guid>
      <description>“Great job, Grant. Dan, that’s fuckin’ terrible.”
Chuck swished his way downstream to me and held out his hand, in which I put the Orvis fly-fishing rod. A gentle wind swayed the branches of the red Vermont Maples lining the stream.
“Too much wrist. You want your whole upper body involved. Like this”, Chuck cast the fly out and let it drift, dangling the brown squirrel-hair lure in front of the rock crags where the rainbow trout were spawning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on Daily Themes</title>
      <link>https://dansramblings.com/posts/story3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dansramblings.com/posts/story3/</guid>
      <description>I’ve changed my mind about myself. I had all these assumptions baked in about who I’m supposed to be in life and I never really tried to figure em out until I took this class. I spent six years working in computers before going back to school, and before that I spent four years studying computers for a computer science degree. Hell, with all that computerin’ I became damn near sure I was just a computer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
